<top_block>
	<navigation_block>
		<link file="#" id="selected">Home</link>
		<link file="#" id="">the journey</link>
		<link file="#" id="">characters</link>
		<link file="#" id="">gallery</link>
		<link file="#" id="">history</link>
	</navigation_block>
	<pattern_block />
	<header_block>
		<title>The Hobbit</title>
		<paragraph>Adventures of Bilbo Baggins</paragraph>
	</header_block>
	<pattern_block />
</top_block>
<content_block>
	<spacer_block />
	<item_block>
		<item_title>An unexpected Party</item_title>
		<item_metadata>Chapter One</item_metadata>
		<item_body>
			<subtitle>Hobbits are introduced</subtitle>
			<paragraph>
				Bilbo Baggins invites Gandalf to tea. The next day
				Gandalf arrives and with him comes thirteen Dwarves.
				After eating they discuss the recovery of the treasure
				that the dragon Smaug took from Erebor, and Bilbo is
				hired as their burglar.
			</paragraph>
			<extimage class="left"
				url="http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/7/7b/Bag_End.jpg/300px-Bag_End.jpg"
				width="" height="" alt_text="" />
		</item_body>
	</item_block>
	<item_block>
		<item_title>Roast Mutton</item_title>
		<item_metadata>Chapter Two</item_metadata>
		<item_body>
			<subtitle>Bilbo and Gandalf meet the dwarves</subtitle>
			<paragraph>
				The next day Bilbo and Gandalf meet the Dwarves at The
				Green Dragon Inn, from there they set off on their
				adventure, Gandalf disappears and they lose some of
				their supplies in a river, then they see a light in the
				trees and send Bilbo to investigate. Bilbo discovers
				three Trolls, and is captured when he attempts to pick
				one of the trolls pockets, when the Dwarves come up the
				trolls are distracted and capture them while Bilbo runs
				and hides. Gandalf tricks the trolls by throwing his
				voice and they fight until dawn, when they are turned to
				stone. Gandalf, Bilbo, and the Dwarves then find the
				cave of the three trolls, within they find swords and
				provisions, before they continue on their journey.
			</paragraph>
			<extimage class="left"
				url="http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/6/67/Thorin_in_blue_mountains.jpg/300px-Thorin_in_blue_mountains.jpg"
				width="" height="" alt_text="" />
		</item_body>
	</item_block>
	<item_block>
		<item_title>A Short Rest</item_title>
		<item_metadata>Chapter Three</item_metadata>
		<item_body>
			<subtitle>
				Gandalf, Bilbo, and the Dwarves headed for Rivendell
			</subtitle>
			<paragraph>
				Gandalf, Bilbo, and the Dwarves headed for Rivendell,
				when they arrived there they stayed for at least
				fourteen days. During which time they were refreshed and
				their provisions restocked, and on the last day of their
				stay Elrond had a look at the swords they had collected
				from the troll cave, he told Gandalf that his sword was
				named Glamdring, and Thorin that his was named Orcrist.
				He also looked at their map, and discovered Moon-letters
				written upon it. The next day they set off on their way
				to the Misty Mountains.
			</paragraph>
			<extimage class=""
				url="http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/6/69/Elrond11.jpg/300px-Elrond11.jpg"
				width="" height="" alt_text="" />
		</item_body>
		<spacer_block />
		<item_body identificador="annotator"></item_body>
	</item_block>
	<divider_block />
</content_block>
<footer_block>
	copyright 2006
	<link file="" id="">Website.com</link>
	. Valid
	<link file="" id="">CSS</link>
	&amp;
	<link file="" id="">XHTML</link>
	. Template design by
	<link file="" id="">Arcsin</link>
</footer_block>
